
 [
    {
      "question": " A form of democracy in which citizens elect officials to govern on their behalf",
      "choice1": "Direct Democracy ",
      "choice2": "Representative Democracy",
      "choice3": "Indirect Democracy",
      "choice4": "Philosopher ",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "A form of democracy in which all citizens can participate firsthand in the decision-making process ",
      "choice1": "Direct Democracy ",
      "choice2": "Representative Democracy",
      "choice3": "Indirect Democracy",
      "choice4": "Philosopher ",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "A person who searches for wisdom or enlightenment",
      "choice1": "Direct Democracy ",
      "choice2": "Representative Democracy",
      "choice3": "Indirect Democracy",
      "choice4": "Philosopher ",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Under whose leadership did Athens experience a Golden Age?",
      "choice1": "Ceasar ",
      "choice2": "God",
      "choice3": "Athena",
      "choice4": "Pericles ",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "who could attend school in Athens",
      "choice1": "boys",
      "choice2": "girls",
      "choice3": "everyone",
      "choice4": "men",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "whose role in Athnes was to learn how to read, play music and teach at home?",
      "choice1": "Men",
      "choice2": "women",
      "choice3": "grandparents",
      "choice4": "children ",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "The Athenian economy was based on what?",
      "choice1": "Farming",
      "choice2": "Trade",
      "choice3": "all of the above",
      "choice4": "none of the above ",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the group that served as a protective and defensive league?",
     "choice1": "Spartan",
      "choice2": "Athens",
      "choice3": "Mob",
      "choice4": "Delian ",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "who fought in the peloponnesian war?",
      "choice1": "Sparta and Athens",
      "choice2": "Greece and Athens",
      "choice3": "Sparta and Greece",
      "choice4": "Athens and America",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The Athenian __________ was based on farming and trade",
      "choice1": "life",
      "choice2": "Economy",
      "choice3": "Culture",
      "choice4": "Housing",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What form of Democracy is when the citizens elect officials to govern on their behalf",
      "choice1": "Representative",
      "choice2": "Indirect",
      "choice3": "Direct",
      "choice4": "Human",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What form of Democracy is when all citizens can participate firsthand in the decision-making process",
      "choice1": "Representative",
      "choice2": "Indirect",
      "choice3": "Direct",
      "choice4": "Human",
      "answer": 1
    }
 ]
